{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Gant",
    "predicate": "property/birthName",
    "object": "Robert John Gonzalez",
    "human_readable": "The birth name of Robert Gant is Robert John Gonzalez.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9279666543006897,
            "question": "What was Robert Gant's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8986713290214539,
            "question": "Does Robert John Gonzalez use his full birth name professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8781415820121765,
            "question": "Is Robert Gant's birth name different from his stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8427870869636536,
            "question": "What are the two given names in Robert Gant's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7020664215087891,
            "question": "What is Robert John Gonzalez's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6493943333625793,
            "question": "How does Robert Gant's birth name compare to his stage name in terms of length?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1325211375951767,
            "question": "What is the significance of a birth name compared to a chosen stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03563487157225609,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other actors who use stage names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01947745494544506,
            "question": "Why might an individual choose to use a different stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01538213063031435,
            "question": "What are the potential benefits of using a stage name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth name of Robert Gant is Robert John Gonzalez.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6471_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might an individual choose to use a different stage name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6471_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of other actors who use stage names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6471_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of a birth name compared to a chosen stage name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6471_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6471_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple as the information in files 10 and 53 explicitly mention that Robert Gant's birth name is Robert John Gonzalez."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the statement \"The birth name of Robert Gant is Robert John Gonzalez\" is supported by the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}